

# Systems Administrator $\Delta$





## WHO AM I?

An organized administrator with a range of skills in systems and network administration. Experienced in working with platforms such as Linux, Windows and Cisco IOS. Possessing extensive knowledge in dealing with problems related to network and system security, backup management, application deployment in high-security environment, SQL database management, and virtualization.



Veeam PRTG ESXi PfSense Git

## **EXPERIENCE**

2021 – Currently Systems Administrator

Atlas International UzDe

Working on Safe City project in Tashkent as main Linux administrator in a secured network.

Linux / Windows / Cisco

2020 – 2021 Assistant System Administrator

Atlas International UzDe

Trial period mostly managing existing Linux servers and Windows workstations for Investment

Project. Getting acquainted with PRTG system monitoring and Veeam Backup solution.

Linux / Windows

### **EDUCATION**

2017 - 2021 **Bachelor's Degree** 

**Bangor University** 

Finance Investment and Risk Management course of Bangor University provided by Management and Investment Institute of Singapore in Tashkent.

**TRAINING** 

2021 CCNA Uzscinet

 ${\tt CCNA\ Network\ Academy\ courses:\ "Introduction\ to\ Networks",\ "Switching,\ Routing,\ and\ Wireless}$ 

Essentials", "Enterprise Networking, Security, and Automation".

2021 Linux Courses Micros Training Centre

Completed training on CentOS and Debian Linux distributions: "Linux Essentials", "Linux System

Administration", "Linux Network Administration".

2021 Windows Courses Micros Training Centre

Completed official Microsoft courses: "Installing and Configuring Windows 10", "Installation, Storage and Compute with Windows Server 2016", "Networking with Windows Server 2016".

#### **LANGUAGES**

**OTHER SKILLS** 

#### HOBBIES

Russian - native English - proficient Uzbek - elementary German - rudimentary Versatility; Adaptability; Fast-learning; Analytical thinking. In spare time I love to work on personal programming projects, weird PC setups, modding and playing video games.